Canyon Cinema Records, ca. 1961-2009 M1681
Stanford University. Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Canyon Cinema Records
ca. 1961-2009
M1681
Stanford University. Department of Special Collections and University Archives
44.0 Linear feet (82 boxes, 4 flat boxes)
Archival records documenting the history and origins of the collective, its various publishing activities, its programs, correspondence with members, data such as sales figures, and other aspects of the organization, as well as the cultural context of the San Francisco Bay Area film-making cultures.
Acquisition Information
Purchased, 2009. Accession 2009-138.
Conditions Governing Access note
No restrictions.
Historical Note
Established in 1961 by filmmakers Bruce Baillie and Chick Strand in the community of Canyon CA, Canyon Cinema has consistent force in the development of independent, avant-garde, personal and counter-cultural filmmaking at the local, national and international levels. Originally a peripatetic film exhibition venue, Canyon Cinema published THE CANYON CINEMANEWS from 1962 through 1982 (and briefly in the mid-'90s). Since 1967 the primary activity of the collective has been the distribution of works by filmmaker members, for rental and sale, primarily in the 16mm, VHS and DVD formats. Works distributed by Canyon remain the property of the artists.
Scope and Contents note
The records of Canyon Cinema, dating from 1962 to 2009 are arranged in five series: Series 1. Publications, Series 2. Filmmakers, Series 3. Administrative records, Series 4. Exhibition records, Series 5. Collected ephemera, and Series 6. Media. These records document the business activities of Canyon Cinema in its capacities as a film distributor, as a film exhibitor and as a publisher of the journal, THE CANYON CINEMANEWS. Files include the complete body of publications created by Canyon Cinema, including THE CANYON CINEMANEWS and all distribution catalogs, well as filmmaker correspondence, business records and exhibition records. Additionally, this collection contains material created outside the organization and collected by it during its years of operation, including publications, exhibition records and artists' ephemera documenting the field of independent filmmaking and exhibition.
Anger, Kenneth; Baillie, Bruce, 1931-; Brakhage, Stan.; Broughton, James, 1913-1999; Connor, Bruce; Iimura, Takahiko, 1937-; Kren, Kurt, 1929-; Kuchar, George, 1942-; Kuchar, Mike, 1942-; Lawder, Standish D.; Nelson, Gunvor; Nelson, Robert; Schneemann, Carolee, 1939-; Sharits, Paul; Varela, Willie, 1950-
- Series 1. Publications
  - Canyon Cinemanews
    - Canyon Cinemanews: June 27, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: Sept. 1962 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: Dec. 1962 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: Vol. 1, No. 2 (Feb. 1963) (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: Vol. 1, No. 3 (March 1963) (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: Vol. 1, No. 4 (April 1963) (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: Vol. 1, No. 5 (May 1963) (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: Vol. 1, No. 6 (June 1963) (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: Vol. 1, No. 7 (Aug. 1963) (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: Vol. 1, No. 8 (Sept. 1963) (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: Vol. 1, No. 9 (Oct. 1963) (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: Vol. 1, No. 10 (Nov. 1963) (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: Vol. 1, No. 11 (1963) (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: Vol. 2, No. 7 (Sept. 1964) (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: April 1965 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: May 1965 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: June-July 1965 (Box 1, Folder 16A)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: Aug. 1965 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: Sept. 1965 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: Oct. 1965 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: Nov-Dec. 1965 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: Jan. 1966 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: Feb. 1966 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: March-April 1966 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: May 1966 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: June 1966 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: July 1966 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: Aug. 1966 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: Sept-Oct. 1966 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: Nov. 1966 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: Dec. 1966-Jan. 1967 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: Feb. 1967 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: March/April 1967 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: May 1967 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: July 1967 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: Aug. 1967 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: Sept-Oct. 1967 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: Nov. 1967 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: Dec. 1967-Jan. 1968 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: Jan-Feb. 1968 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: April-May 1968 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: May-July 1968 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: July-Aug. 1968 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: Aug-Sept. 1968 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: 68-7 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: 68-8 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: 69-1 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: 69-2 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: 69-3 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: 69-4 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: 69-5 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: 69-6 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: 69-7 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: 70-1 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: 70-2 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: 70-3 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: 70-4 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: 71-1 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: 71-2 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: 71-3 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: 72-1 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: 72-2 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: 72-3 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: 72-4 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: 72-5/6 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: 73-1 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: 73-2/3 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: 73-4/5 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Canyon Cinemanews 73-6 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: 74-1 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: 74-2 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: 74-3 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: 74-4 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: 74-5 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: 74-6 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: 75-1 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: 75-2 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: 75-3 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: 75-4 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: 75-5 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: 75-6 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: 76-1 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: 76-2 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: 76-3 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: 76-4 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: 76-5 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: 76-6 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: 77-1 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: 77-2 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: 77-3 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: 77-4 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: 77-5 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: 77-6 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: 78-1 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: 78-2 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: 78-3/4 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: 78-5 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: 78-6/79-1 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Cinemanews 79-5/6 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Cinemanews 80-1/2 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Cinemanews 80-3/4/5 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Cinemanews 80-6/1981-1 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Cinemanews 81-2/3/4/5/6 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Canyon Cinema Newsletter: Vol. 1, No. 1 (1985) (Flat-box 49, Folder 4)
    - Canyon Cinema Newsletter No. 2, Jan. 1986 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - New Canyon Cinemanews: 94-1 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - New Canyon Cinemanews: 95-1 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - New Canyon Cinemanews: 95-2 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - New Canyon Cinemanews: 95-3 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: 95-4 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: 96-1 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: 96-2 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Canyon Cinemanews: Feb-Apr. 1986, 1968 (Flat-box 48, Folder 1)
  - Distribution Catalogs
    - Canyon Cinema Distribution Catalog 1, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Canyon Cinema Distribution Catalog 2 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Canyon Cinema Distribution Catalog 2, Supplement 1 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Canyon Cinema Distribution Catalog 2, Supplement 2 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Canyon Cinema Distribution Catalog 2, Supplement 3 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Canyon Cinema Distribution Catalog 2, Supplement 4 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Canyon Cinema Distribution Catalog 3 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Canyon Cinema Distribution Catalog 3, Supplement 1 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Canyon Cinema Distribution Catalog 3, Supplement 2 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Canyon Cinema Distribution Catalog 4 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Canyon Cinema Distribution Catalog 4, Supplement 1 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Canyon Cinema Distribution Catalog 4, Supplement 2 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Canyon Cinema Distribution Catalog 5 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Canyon Cinema Distribution Catalog 5, Supplement (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Canyon Cinema Distribution Catalog: Update 1984 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Canyon Cinema Distribution Catalog: Update 1985 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Canyon Cinema Distribution Catalog: Update 1986 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Canyon Cinema Distribution Catalog 6 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Canyon Cinema Distribution Catalog: Supplement 1986 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Canyon Cinema Distribution Catalog: Supplement 1990 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Canyon Cinema Distribution Catalog 7 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Canyon Cinema Distribution Catalog: Supplement 1994 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Canyon Cinema Distribution Catalog 2000 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Canyon Cinema Distribution Catalog 2, Supplement 1 (annotated) (Box 53, Folder 3)
      General note
      Annotated
    - Canyon Cinema Distribution Catalog 3 (torn pages) (Box 53, Folder 4)
      contains deliberately torn pages
    - Canyon Cinema Distribution Catalog 3 (annotated) (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Canyon Cinema Distribution Catalog 3: Addendum, 1972 (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - Directory of Independent Films and Their Sources (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Canyon Cinema Members Newsletter, 1973 (Flat-box 85, Folder 1)
  - Galley proofs and designs (Flat-box 89)
  - Galley proofs and designs (Flat-box 90)
- Series 2. Filmmakers
  - Abrams, Jerry (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Adelstein, Gary (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Ahwesh, Peggy (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Ahwesh, Peggy (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Allen, John (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Alvarez, Alfonso (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Anger, Kenneth (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Anger, Kenneth (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Anger, Kenneth (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Angerame, Dominic (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Angerame, Dominic (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Angerame, Dominic (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Angerame, Dominic (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Angerame, Dominic (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Angerame, Dominic (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Arledge, Sara Kathryn (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Arlyck, Ralph (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Arnold, Martin (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Auslender, Leland (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Avery, Caroline (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Babeth (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Baillie, Bruce (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Baillie, Bruce (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Baillie, Bruce (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Baillie, Bruce (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Baillie, Bruce (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Baillie, Bruce (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Bain, Claire (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Baldwin, Craig (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Ball, Gordon (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Barber, Stephanie (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Barnett, Daniel (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Bartlett, Scott (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Barton, Colin (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Bastajian, Tina (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Beckett, Adam (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Beckman, Ericka (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Beeman, Andrea (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Beeson, Coni (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Behrens, John (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Benning, James (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Berliner, Alan (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Berman, Wallace (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Beroes, Stephanie (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Bienstock, David (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Beirmann, Gregg (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Blank, Les (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Blau, Dick (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Block, Beth (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Block, Elizabeth (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Bodien, Earl (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Bokanowski, Patrick (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Bourque, Louise (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Brakhage, Stan (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Brakhage, Stan (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Brakhage, Stan (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Brakhage, Stan (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Brakhage, Stan (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Brakhage, Stan (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Brakhage, Stan (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Brand, Bill (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Breer, Robert (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Bromberg, Betzy (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Brooks, David (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Brose, Lawrence (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Broughton, James (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Broughton, James (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Brown, Bill (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Brown, Carl E. (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Brown, Carl E. (Box 12, Folder 1)
    Beat Fatigues: A Series of Exhalations-Film Writings/History 1981-1991
  - Burckhardt, Rudy (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Caldararo, Nicolo (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Cameron, Donna (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Cannizzaro, John (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Carducci, Gina (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Carney, John (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Carpenter, Maia Cybelle (Box 12, Folder 8)
    File includes data CD
  - Child, Abigail (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Chodorov, Pip (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Clarke, Shirley (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Cogan, Christopher (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Conner, Bruce (Box 12, Folder 13)
    Film Stills
  - Conner, Bruce (Box 12, Folder 14)
    Print Sale Inquiries
  - Conner, Bruce (Box 12, Folder 15)
    Print Sales
  - Conner, Bruce (Box 12, Folder 16)
    Misc. Materials
  - Conner, Bruce (Box 13, Folder 1)
    Print Sales 1989-c.2007
  - Conner, Bruce (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Conner, Bruce (Box 13, Folder 3)
    Print Sales 2007-c.2009
  - Conner, Bruce (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Conner, Bruce (Box 13, Folder 5)
    Inventory of Films
  - Conner, Bruce (Box 14, Folder 1)
    Reviews and Announcements
  - Conner, Bruce (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Conner, Bruce (Box 14, Folder 3)
    Correspondence post-1993
  - Conner, Bruce (Box 14, Folder 4)
    Correspondence pre-1993
  - Eames, Demetrios (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Deutsch, Gustav (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Devaux, Frederique (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Doberman, Gary (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Dorsky, Nathaniel (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Dwoskin, Steve (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Dye, Steven (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Eisenberg, Daniel (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Engel, Jules (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Elam, JoAnn (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Elder, R. Bruce (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Emshwiller, Ed (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Engel, Jules (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Export, Valie (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Faccinto, Victor (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Farley, William (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Fergus, Corwin (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Findley, Janice (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Fischinger, Oskar (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Fleisch, Thorsten (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Fleming, Michele (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Flowers, Robert Daniel (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Fonoroff, Nina (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Friedrich, Su (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Froehle, Paula (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Fuchs, Sallie (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Fulton, Robert (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Garfield, Ar (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Gatten, David (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Gearey, Dave (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Gehr, Ernie (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Geiser, Janie (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Geyer, Anna (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Gibbons, Joe (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Glabicki, Paul (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Glass, Allen D. II (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Goldberg, Gary (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Goldsmith, Silvianna (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Gottheim, Larry (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Gray, Michael (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Greenfield, Amy (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Grenier, Vincent (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Griffin, George (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Gutman, Walter (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Haack, Warren (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Halm, Patrick (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Halpern, Amy (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Hammer, Barbara (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Hancox, Rick (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Hansen, Brian (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Harris, Christopher (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Haynes, Doug (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Heit, Laura (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Henny, Leonard (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Henny, Leonard (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Henry, Walter (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Heller, Eve (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Hershey, Barry (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Hills, Henry (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Hindle, Will (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Hindle, Will (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Hoffman, Philip (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Hoffman, Philip (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Hubbard, Jim (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Holmes, Karen (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Hudina, Chuck (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Hull, Jamie (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Folder received empty.
  - Humbert, Nicolas and Werner Penzel (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Huot, Robert (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Hutton, Peter (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Iimura, Takahiko (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Iimura, Takahiko (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Iimura, Takahiko (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Iimura, Takahiko (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Irwin, James (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Jacobs, Ken (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Jacobson, Sarah (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Jacoby, Roger (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Johnston, Denah A. (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Jones, William E. (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Jordan, Lawrence (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Kano, Shiho (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Kaplan, Helene (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Keller, Marjorie (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Kessler, Chester (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Kirby, Lynn Marie (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Kitchen, Diane (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Klahr, Lewis (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Kless, Larry (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Klutinis, Barbara (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Knowland, Bill (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Kobland, Ken (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Kovacoda, Milada (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Krahn, Angelina (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Krasilovsky, Alexis (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Kren, Kurt (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Kren, Kurt (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Krumins, Daina (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Kubelka, Peter (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Kuchar, George (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Kuchar, George (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Kuchar, George (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Kuchar, George (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Land, Owen (Box 21, Folder 1)
    aka George Landow
  - LaPore, Mark (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Lawder, Standish (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Lawder, Standish (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Leger, Jackie (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Lehmann, Andre (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Levine, Charles (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Levine, Saul (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Lewis, Brady (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Lieber, Edvard (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Linder, Carl (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Linkevitch, Barbara (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Liotta, Jeanne (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Lipman, Ross (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Lipton, Lenny (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Lipzin, Janis (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Lothar, Eva (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Lowder, Rose (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Lye, Len (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Maas, Willard (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - MacLennan, Toby (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Maliga, Sandy (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Massarella, Josephine (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - McCabe, Kate (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - McCall, Anthony (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - McCormick, Matt (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - McDowell, Curt (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Mekas, Jonas (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Mekas, Jonas (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Menken, Marie (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Merritt, Toney (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Meyer, Andrew (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Moore, Andy (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Morrison, Bill (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Muller, Matthias (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Murphy, J.J. (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Murray, Julie (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Myers, Richard (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Nagler, Sol (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Nelson, Gunvor (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Nelson, Robert (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Nelson, Robert (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Nigrin, Albert Gabriel (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Nigrin, Albert Gabriel (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Nigrin, Albert Gabriel (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Nigrin, Albert Gabriel (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Nishikawa, Tomonari (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - O'Neill, Pat (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - O., Dore (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Orr, Jerry (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Otis, James (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Padula, Fred (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Palazzolo, Tom (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Palazzolo, Tom (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Patrick, Brian (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Patrick, Eric (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Pearson, Lyle (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Perkins, Phil (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Peterson, Sidney (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Petrick, Howard (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Pierce, Leighton (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Pitt, Suzan (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Plays, Dana (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Plotnick, Danny (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Pohjola, Ilppo (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Polta, Steve (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Povey, Thad (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Price, Luther (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Pryce, Charlotte (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Pucill, Sarah (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Ralph Records (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Ravett, Abraham (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Rea, Raymond (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Reed, Mary Beth (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Richardson, Emily (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Rimmer, David (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Rosas-Walsh, Michael (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Rose, Peter (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Rosenblatt, Jay (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Rosenthal, Ken Paul (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Sachs, Lynn (Box 26, Folder 17)
    File includes two floppy discs
  - Sackl, Albert (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Schaller, Robert (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Scher, Jeff (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Schmidt, Rick (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Schneemann, Carolee (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Schofill, John Luther (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Seibert, Jim (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Severson, Anne (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Sharits, Greg (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Sharits, Paul (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Sharits, Paul (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Sher, Elizabeth (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Sherman, David (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Sherman, David (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Sherman, David (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Sherman, Stuart (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Sherwin, Guy (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Silva, Michelle (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Single Spark Films (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Skoller, Jeffrey (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Smith, Cauleen (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Smith, Jack (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Smith, John (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Snider, Greta (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Snider, Greta (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Snow, Michael (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Solomon, Phil (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Sonbert, Warren (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Spinello, Barry (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Stanley, Karen (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Stark, Scott (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Stauffacher, Frank (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Steers, Stacy (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Steiner, Konrad (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Stewart, Alexander (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Stookey, Jeff (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Storz, Bill (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Strand, Chick (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Street, Mark (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Sullivan, Chris (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Takabishi, Noriko (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Todd, Peter (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Tscherkassky, Peter (Box 29, Folder 1)
    File includes zip disk
  - Tucker, David (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Turkle, Tyler (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Uman, Naomi (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Ungerer, Walter (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Vanderbeek, Stan (Box 29, Folder 6)